http://www.rileymed.com/en/content/data-policy

INFORMATION WE COLLECT
To provide an excellent customer service experience, we need to know a little about you. Below is an outline of what information SymmetrySurgical.com collects, and how we collect it.
When you sign up for a SymmetrySurgical.com account, all your activities on SymmetrySurgical.com are tied to this account. In the chart below, we’ve detailed the information we may collect about you, depending on your activities on our website and how we obtain this information.
What We Collect
How We Collect It
Your name
We require you to provide a legal name when you request a Web Account, submit a New Customer Form, request to be contacted by one of our Specialists, or use our Live Chat feature on SymmetrySurgical.com.
Your email address
We require you to provide a valid email address when you request a Web Account, submit a New Customer Form, request to be contacted by one of our Specialists, or use our Live Chat feature on SymmetrySurgical.com.
Your IP Address, which is a designator that is automatically assigned to your computer
An IP address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever you use our platform and services, along with the time of your visit and the specific page(s) that you visited.
Your Facility’s Name
We require you to provide a legal facility name when you request a Web Account, submit a New Customer Form, or request to be contacted by one of our Specialists on SymmetrySurgical.com.
We also use the IP service Lead Forensics to suggest your facility name from your IP address. This enables us to better serve our web visitors and show more targeted content that may be of interest to them.
Your Facility’s Postal Address
We require you to provide a legal facility address when you submit a New Customer Form on SymmetrySurgical.com
As mentioned above, we use the IP service Lead Forensics to suggest your facility’s address from your IP address. This enables us to better serve our web visitors and show more targeted content that may be of interest to them.
Your Facility’s Telephone Number
We require you to provide a valid phone number for your Facility when you submit a New Customer Form on SymmetrySurgical.com.
As mentioned above, we use the IP service Lead Forensics to suggest your facility’s telephone number from your IP address. This enables us to better serve our web visitors and show more targeted content that may be of interest to them.
Your specific activities on or connected to the SymmetrySurgical.com platform. These might include web sets you have created, products you have favorited, products and pages you have viewed, and products added to your cart.
When you are signed in or identified as a SymmetrySurgical.com user, your activities on or connected to the SymmetrySurgical.com platform are associated with your account.
Any other information you voluntarily submit
You may be offered the choice to provide additional information to us. For example, we may collect information when you initiate a Live Chat with our customer service team or if we assist you by telephone.
The name of the browser you use to access SymmetrySurgical.com
Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows PC or Mac), device type (PC, mobile phone, tablet), screen resolution, operating system name and version, device manufacturer and model, language, and the internet browser type and version. Collecting this information helps us build and deliver the best possible version of SymmetrySurgical.com to you.
Information collected through cookies as disclosed in our linked Cookies Policy
We, and/or our service providers may use cookies, pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs), and other similar technologies to understand user activities. Like other websites, SymmetrySurgical.com will not function properly if cookies are not enabled. We use third-party analytics services like Google Analytics provided by Google Inc. (“Google”), Marketo service provided by Marketo (“Marketo”) and Lead Forensic service provided by “Lead Forensics.” These analytics services may use cookies and similar technologies to analyze how people use our web site and services and provide statistical reports about aggregate user behavior. Such services may also collect information about platform visitors’ use of other websites. Please review our Cookies Policy for detailed information regarding the cookies we use and how you can manage them.
The transaction amount you purchased through our purchase page
Your billing address, purchase order and transaction amount is collected on our payment page when an order is initiated. We currently do not accept credit card or bank number, or expiration date information on our SymmetrySurgical.com payment page. Our customer service team will reach out by phone to collect this information after an order is placed on our website.
Some of the information above reveals your specific identity, or is directly tied to your specific identity, such as your name and email address. Some of this information does not reveal your specific identity, or does not directly relate to you, such as your browser and device information or information collected through cookies. If we ever combine non-personally identifiable information with personally identifiable information, the combined information will be treated by us as personally identifying information and protected accordingly.
Our services are not directed to people under the age of eighteen (18), and we do not knowingly collect personal information from them.
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
Here are the ways we might use your information to run our platform, provide our services and serve you better content
Purpose
Examples
Providing the functionality of our platform. We engage in these activities to manage our relationship with you.
• To send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding your orders, our services and/or policies.
• To ensure that our site and applications function properly and are optimized for your computer or device and to store your preferences and settings.
To fulfill your specific requests through the platform. We engage in these activities to manage our relationship with you.
• To allow you to create clinical sets, favorite products, access your invoices and order history, as well as to complete and fulfill your transactions with us.
• To allow you to send email messages that you choose to send to your contacts through our platform, such as to share a clinical set or cart list. By using this feature, you guarantee that you have the right to use and provide us the email addresses you submit.
Accomplishing our business purposes. We engage in these activities to manage our relationship with you, to comply with a legal obligation, because we have a legitimate interest, and/or with your consent.
• For data analysis, for example, to improve the efficiency of our services.
• For audits, to verify that our internal processes function as intended and are compliant with legal, regulatory, or contractual requirements.
• For fraud and security monitoring purposes, for example to detect and prevent cyber-attacks or attempts to commit identity theft.
• For developing new products, features, and services.
• For enhancing, improving or modifying our platform.
• For identifying usage trends, for example, understanding which parts of our platform are of most interest to users.
• For determining the effectiveness of campaigns.
• For operating and expanding our business activities, for example, understanding which parts of our platform are of most interest to our users so we can focus on energies on meeting our users’ interests.
• For legal compliance. In rare circumstances, we may have to use and disclose information we have about our users in order to exercise or protect legal rights or defend against legal claims under applicable law.
• We use cookies and similar technologies as detailed in our Cookies Policy to measure and improve our services and develop features and functionalities on our platform. For example, if we see that people using a certain device use the platform the most, we might decide to build content specifically for that type of device.
Analysis of information for business reporting and providing personalized services. We provide personalized services either with your consent or because we believe you have a legitimate interest.
• To personalize your experience by presenting products and offers tailored to you based on information we have collected from you.
To share marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you. We engage in this activity with your consent, or to manage our relationship with you.
• Communications related to your field, industry or location that may be relevant to you.
• To allow you to participate in similar promotions.
• Most marketing communications will be sent via email and sometimes through direct mail to your facility’s address.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information, which we think you may find interesting, with your consent.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) which applies to all 28 EU member states, and the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information we have retained that pertains to you please write to
Symmetry Surgical
Marketing Department
3034 Owen Dr,
Antioch, TN, 37013
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
CONTACT US
customerservice@symmetrysurgical.com
export@symmetrysurgical.com
US & CANADA: +1 800-251-3000INTERNATIONAL: +1 615-964-5532
Catalog
CAREERS
©2019 SYMMETRY SURGICAL INC ALL RIGHTS RESERVEDThis Website, or any part thereof, may not be reproduced in any form. Not all products are available in all countries. Symmetry Surgical reserves the right to add, modify or discontinue products as necessary, with or without notice. Symmetry Surgical respects the intellectual property rights of all of its suppliers, vendors, competitors and other third parties. If you have any intellectual property rights concerns with anything appearing on this Website, please let us know by contacting us at 1.800.251.3000. The S logo and SYMMETRY SURGICAL are registered trademarks of Symmetry Surgical, Inc.
Your session has been terminated due to inactivity, please login again.
